tumbleinto.com 2016-11-06

# Privacy Policy | Tumbleinto

This policy describes how and why Tumbleinto collects non-personally identifiable data from users and website visitors to http://www.tumbleinto.com, and how that data will be used. Tumbleinto is committed to respecting the privacy of non-personal identifiable data gathered.

Tumbleinto’s Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the tumbleinto.com Terms of Use. Each time that you access or use the Site you signify that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by the Terms of Use, and this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue using our Services.

**1\. Information That Is Collected**

Tumbleinto understands the importance of maintaining your privacy, and strives to provide services with your security in mind. You will be asked for consent if your personal information is to be used in a way other than originally intended. For us to identify which areas of Tumbleinto are used the most and provide statistical analysis of the site, we will record information such as your browser type, IP address, timestamp information and the pages you’ve viewed. This will help us make site enhancements and offer you the highest quality experience possible

Tumbleinto will ask you for and keep a record of personal information, including name, email address, login time, and Facebook profile photo. You may change these details and settings on your account page. Submissions you make through Tumbleinto may be saved or exhibited publicly on the website, in order to provide the most complete version of our services. “Submissions” refers to any material you post to Tumbleinto or information displayed on your profile.

We will record certain information that you provide in feedback, questions, or registered complaints in order to efficiently respond to your questions or concerns.

**2\. Information you provide to us**

In order to provide the Services, we collect the following types of information from you:

Non-Personal Information/ Anonymous Data (automatically collected information which doesn’t identify the user).

Non-personal/anonymous data is any data or information that does not personally identify you. We obtain non-personal information about you from information that you provide to us, either separately or together with your personally identifiable information. We also automatically collect certain non-personal information from you when you use our Services and may include such information as your Internet Protocol address, your browser, recent search history, and your activity on our websites or website of our partners.

We use non-personally identifiable data collected from users and website visitors in order to:

1) To improve the quality of the website & enhance your experience or for other internal and statistical purposes.

2) To enforce our terms of use.

3) To comply with any applicable law and assist law enforcement agencies as required.

4) To conduct surveys and market researches.

5) We may use anonymous, statistical or aggregated information about the website’s use and share, publish, post, disseminate, transmit or otherwise communicate or make available such information, to suppliers, business partners, sponsors, affiliates and any other third party, at our sole discretion.

**3\. How This Information Is Used**

Your personal information may be accessed by affiliates of Tumbleinto, such as our parent company, subsidiaries, or joint ventures, that are currently with us or have the potential to be with us in the future. These affiliates are obligated to honor this privacy policy. If another company obtains Tumbleinto, that company will then possess your personal information. However, they too are under strict obligation to honor the claims of this privacy policy. Third parties that work with Tumbleinto may receive submissions you make through the website, which may end up being published on their sites or platforms. This information includes your account name, but not your personal information, unless it was listed in the submission.

Information related to user behavior may be disclosed to third parties in connection with a present or future business partnership. This includes information relating to users that have clicked advertising banners and the number of users visiting our site.

When you visit Tumbleinto, you will see advertisements from third parties displayed on the site. Information about your visit to the site may be used by these companies, not including your name, email address, or telephone number. This helps them choose advertisements that you would find most interesting. Click here for more information about our advertising process, or not having your information used by these third parties

**4\. Cookies , Web Beacons and Log Files**

Cookies may be used on some pages of our site. Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing a more customized website experience. For more detailed information please visit our Cookie Declaration.

**Cookies:** When you use our Services, we may send one or more “cookies” (small data files) to your computer to uniquely identify your browser and enable us to help you log in faster and generally enhance your navigation through the Services. Cookies save you time, for example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within the Services, a cookie recalls your specific information on subsequent visits. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the website uses to track the pages you’ve visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A persistent cookie remains on your computer after you close your browser so that it can be used by your browser on subsequent visits to use the Services. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. In addition to enhancing the user experience, we may use cookies to track traffic user traffic patterns. We do this to determine the usefulness and efficiency of our Services and its various pages, and to analyze traffic patterns, in order to constantly improve the Services and better serve our customers.

**Web Beacons/Pixel Tracking:** Tumbleinto.com may employ a common technique usually referred to as “pixel tracking” to measure the effectiveness of marketing and advertisements, as well as compile aggregate usage statistics. Pixel tracking, which may be used in connection with advertisements on other sites, on our website or in e-mail messages, involves the use of pixel tags (also known as “clear gifs,” “Web beacons” or “1-by-1 gifs”) that are not visible to the user of the site and consist of a few lines of computer coding. For example, if you visit our website from an advertisement on another site, the pixel tag will reference the cookie you received when you clicked on the advertisement. The pixel tag also may register this activity with a business partner to allow us to count the number of times or when an advertisement is accessed. This data is collected for use in our marketing and research. Personally identifiable information about you is not collected by pixel tracking, nor is any tracking information generated from the pixel tag allowed to be used for any other purpose other than to report website activity to us.

**5\. Changes to Policy**

From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy. Therefore, it is recommended that you read it periodically. All substantial changes made to this policy will be notified on the website, at our sole discretion, and will take effect immediately.

**6 . Contact us**

Please direct all questions in connection with this privacy policy via our _contact us_ form.
